Okay, next exercise.
那么在这个练习里
We're going to examine images in media, and
我们将会学习如何在我们的网页中
how we can include them into our webpages.
通过应用多媒体来插入图像
First step, download the image dubbed zip file that we have provided for you.
首先我们需要下载已经提供了的 一个 zip 文件
Move the zip file to the confusion folder, unzip it.
将这个 zip 解压后得到的 img 文件夹
You'll be left with a folder named img in the confusion folder.
移进我们的 confusion 文件夹中
This img folder contains
这个 img 文件夹里面包含了
all the images that we're gonna make use of in this exercise.
我们做这个练习所需的所有图像
Next, let's open our project in brackets and
然后 在 brackets 中打开我们的项目
then have a look at the current state of the webpage.
然后看看我们现在的网页长啥样
In particular, we'll be updating the index for
我们接下来要做的是用一些图像 和多媒体对象
our HTML page by adding some images and media objects into this pitch.
更新我们的 index.html 文件
So looking at the current state of the webpage, you'll see that there is hardly
那么先看看我们现在这个网页 你会发现它相当"无趣"
any images on this webpage, and it looks fairly bland.
因为它没有包含任何的图像 而图像将是 一个网页漂亮与否的关键
Well of course we had to wait until we learned about images in media
当然了 想要在我们的网页中插入图像的话
before we could add these to our webpage.
你需要先学学怎么应用多媒体来插入图像
So in this exercise we are going to add images and
而这正是这个练习所需要做的事
media to make the webpage a little more exciting to look at.
完成这个练习后 这个网页看上去 就会有趣多了
As our first step in adding images to this webpage,
那么我们想加进的第一个图像
we are going to add the restaurant's logo to this webpage.
就是我们这个餐厅的 logo
Now you see that there is some space to the right hand side in this jumbotron.
你可以看到我们在超大屏幕的右手边 预留了一些空位
We are going to the put the restaurant's logo in that location in the jumbotron.
我们要做的就是把我们的 logo 放在那
In addition, you recall that in the nav bar we had used the brand,
你可能还会注意到我们页面左上角 有一个商标
link there, and we'll use just text there to represent the name of the restaurant.
现在那里还只是些纯文字而已
We're gonna replace that with the logo of this restaurant.
我们将会用 logo 替换掉它
Going to our index.html page, we first scroll down to the jumbotron.
那么进入代码部分 我们得先找到 我们实现超大屏幕的地方
In the jumbotron, I'm going to replace the second
在这块代码中 我们需要用我们的 logo 部分的代码
column that we have there by the restaurant's logo.
替换掉这里第二列部分的代码
So we're going to use an image for the restaurant's logo and then replace that
具体而言 我们在这个代表第二列的 div 标签下
div class, or include the image into the div class.
插入一个代表我们 logo 的 img 标签
And then update the div class appropriately.
然后再做一些排版上的微调
So let's do that.
让我们回车
And then we'll come back and examine the code.
然后你可以看看我写了哪些代码
So here I have replaced the div class.
正如我之前所说 我插入了一个 img 标签 并做了一些排版
Now, I have reduced the size of the div class to two column widths.
你需要注意的是我将 div 原来的 col-sm-4 类 改成了 col-sm-2 类
So I updated column sm to column sm 2 rather than column sm 4 which was earlier.
也就是说我想让 small 屏幕下的这个图像 占据 2 列而不是原来的 4 列
Now I'm going to use the remaining two columns for
然后我将会在之后的大作业里
some other purpose in the assignment, so we're gonna leave that as such.
利用上这里我省下的这两列
Inside this div,
在这个 div 里面
now you see that I have included the image of the restaurant's logo there.
你需要注意一下我是怎么实现这个 代表 logo 的 img 标签的
So I'm using image, and the class that I'm using for this image is img-responsive.
我在这里设置了 class=img-responsive
What this means is that this image will automatically adapt to
这意味着这个图像将会是响应式的
the size of the containing parent element which is the div class.
也就是说这个图像的大小能自动调节
So, as the div class's size changes from different screen
当外层的 div 大小随屏幕大小改变时
widths, the restaurant logo image will automatically adapt.
这个 img 的大小也能随之进行改变
This is part of Bootstrap's class support for sponsored images.
这是 Bootstrap 类对响应式图像的支持方式之一
While we are at it, we will as well update the navbar.
当我们做完这个后 我们会对我们的导航栏 进行类似的操作
In the navbar you'll see that we have the a tag with the navbar brand class.
你可以看到我们现在的导航栏里面有一个设置了 class="navbar-brand" 的 a 标签
We're going to replace that navbar brand inside of the text.
我们将会用我们的 logo
We're gonna replace it with the image of our restaurant's logo.
替换掉这里面的文字
And then I will size the image appropriately, so
然后为了让页面好看
that it can be nicely placed in the navbar.
我们需要调整图像的大小
After updating the code inside the a tag, you can now see that I have replaced
现在我把更新后的代码
the text with an image which is the logo of our restaurant.
呈现了出来
I am using the height and width attributes of this image to control the size
我在这里用了 height 属性和 width 属性
of the logo that is displayed in the nav bar.
来控制这个 logo 的大小
After making these changes,
当我们码完了这些代码后
let's go and have a look at the current state of our webpage.
让我们看看我们的网页变成怎么样了吧
Going back to our webpage,
回到我们的网页
you can now see that the restaurant's logo is included in the jumbotron.
你可以看到我们的 logo 出现在了超大屏幕里
In addition, in the nav bar you can see that
而且你也可以看到我们网页的左上角处
the restaurant's name has been replaced with the logo of the restaurant.
我们的 logo 被装进了我们的导航栏里
Now if you click on the logo, you're going to be taken back to the home page.
当你单击这里这个 logo 时 它将把你 导航至主页
Go ahead and apply the same changes to both the jumbotron and the navbar.
接下来我们要做的
In contactus.html file and also the aboutus.html file.
就是对 aboutus.html 等其它文件也做 类似的更新
Remember that all these should have uniform
需要注意的是
design of the jumbotron and the navbar.
你要保证你的设计具有一致性
So, go ahead and make those changes to the remaining two HTML files also.
那么现在就去把这些更新做了吧
And then we'll go to the next step.
当你完成了这些更新后 我们就可以 继续往下走了
After updating the remaining two HTML pages, you will see
需要注意的是 在完成更新后
that when you navigate to those pages, you will see the logo in the navbar.
每一个页面的超大屏幕和左上角的导航栏中
And also in the jumbotron.
都应该要有我们的 logo
Our next step is to use the media object class
我们下一步要学习如何使用 Bootstrap 中的
in Bootstrap to update the descriptions
多媒体对象类来更新我们在 index.html 这些行里
that we have in the rows of our index.html page.
的这些描述
So now you see that in the first row we have the description of our dish there,
你可以看到 我们在第一行里描述了一道菜
and in the third row we have information about our master chef.
而在第三行里我们介绍了我们的主厨
So we're going to use the media object classes to update these
我们将要做的是用多媒体对象类来通过 插入图像
two to include both images as well as the content as such.
之类的方法使我们这些描述变得更丰富多彩
I'm not going to update the content in the second row.
我不会对第二行进行更新
That will be left as an exercise for you in the second assignment.
因为那将是你们要在第二个大作业里 完成的任务
Getting back to the index.html page, we are now going to replace this
回到代码 我们现在要用一个多媒体对象
description that we have for our dish there with a media object.
来替换掉这里的这些描述
I am going to include an image that we already provide for you in the img folder.
我将会引入一个已经在 img 文件夹里 提供的图像
And also, update the remaining contents there to make
与此同时我会将剩下的内容都囊括进 一个多媒体对象
use of the media object to display the description.
这样就可以使这些内容更漂亮地呈现出来
You can now see that I have used the media class applied
现在你可以看到我已经对这个外层 div 设置了
to a div and inside of the div, I am using the media left and
class="media" 而且在这个 div 里面 我用了两个内层 div
the media middle class applied to an inner div.
对其中的一个 我设置了 class="media-left media-middle"
Which includes the images of the dish.
这个 div 将会包含一个图像
Also, the description itself, what was earlier in the div,
同时 对于原本的那些描述 我将它放进了另一个 div
now I have moved into a media-body div in there, the description as it exists.
对这个 div 我设置了 class="media-body"
The h2 tag that is showing the name of the dish.
而在这个 div 里面我放了一个 h2 标签 来显示这道菜的名字
I am using the media heading class for the h2 tag there.
且对这个 h2 标签 我设置了 class="media-heading"
Also, while I'm at it, I also updated the a class that contains
同时 我在最后加了一个 a 标签
the mode link there, to turn it into a button.
这个 a 标签将会是一个按钮 上面写着 More
Moving to the third rule that contains the information about our executive chef.
让我们转到介绍我们主厨的第三行
I have also updated the using the media object.
我同样用多媒体对象更新了这里的内容
So I am including an image of the chef.
我加入了一个主厨的头像
And also shifted the description into the media body class in there.
同时把那些描述移进了 media-body
Finally in the second row,
最后来看第二行
I am just updating the mole link there to turn it into a button.
我只加进了一个 More 按钮
With this we complete all the updates to the index.html page.
当你完成了上述的种种后 你就已经完成了 对 index.html 的更新了
Let's save it and then go and
让我们保存一下并看看
have a look at the final version of the index.html page.
我们现在的 index.html 长啥样
Returning to our webpage, you will now see that in the webpage
回到我们的网页 你可以看到 现在我们的网页中
the description of our dish has been replaced by a media object.
对菜式的描述是装在一个多媒体对象里的
You can notice that we have included an image.
你也可以看到这里有张图
I'm using the image to the image there and
我是用一个 img 标签来引入这张图的
then the description on the right-hand side.
然后我们的描述是在右手边的
Notice how the More link has been updated into a button there.
注意到下面这里有个 More 按钮
In the second row also, you see there are more data to a button.
而在第二行 这里也有一个 More 按钮
And in the last row, again, you see the description of
然后就是最后一行 你可以看到 我们对主厨的描述也更新了
the Executive Chef updated, with a picture of the Executive Chef in place.
你可以在这里看到主厨的头像
This completes this exercise.
以上 我们完成了这次练习
In this exercise we used the image
在本次练习中 我们亲自实现了
classes and the media object class available within Bootstrap
在我们的网页中应用 Bootstrap 支持的
to include images onto our web page.
图像类和多媒体对象类 【翻译 - Carefree0910】